[
    {
       "question": "🇬🇷",
        "response": "اليونان"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇫🇮",
        "response": "فنلندا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇩🇰",
        "response": "الدنمارك"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇰🇭",
        "response": "كمبوديا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇲🇽",
        "response": "المكسيك"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇬🇲",
        "response": "غامبيا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇦🇷",
        "response": "الأرجنتين"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇸🇱",
        "response": "سيراليون"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇦🇿",
        "response": "أذربيجان"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇨🇭",
        "response": "سويسرا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇲🇷",
        "response": "موريتانيا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇩🇯",
        "response": "جيبوتي"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇵🇹",
        "response": "البرتغال"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇳🇴",
        "response": "النرويج"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇨🇾",
        "response": "قبرص"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇺🇸",
        "response": "أمريكا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇷🇺",
        "response": "روسيا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇨🇳",
        "response": "الصين"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇬🇧",
        "response": "بريطانيا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇮🇳",
        "response": "الهند"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇩🇪",
        "response": "ألمانيا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇫🇷",
        "response": "فرنسا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇨🇦",
        "response": "كندا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇧🇷",
        "response": "البرازيل"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇮🇹",
        "response": "إيطاليا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇪🇸",
        "response": "أسبانيا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇦🇺",
        "response": "أستراليا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇿🇦",
        "response": "أفريقيا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇰🇷",
        "response": "كوريا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇳🇱",
        "response": "هولندا"
    },
            {
       "question": "🇸🇪",
        "response": "السويد"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇴🇲",
        "response": "عمان"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇰🇼",
        "response": "الكويت"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇾🇪",
        "response": "اليمن"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇸🇾",
        "response": "سوريا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇯🇴",
        "response": "الأردن"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇹🇳",
        "response": "تونس"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇱🇾",
        "response": "ليبيا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇮🇶",
        "response": "العراق"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇧🇩",
        "response": "بنجلاديش"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇲🇾",
        "response": "ماليزيا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇦🇫",
        "response": "أفغانستان"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇸🇩",
        "response": "السودان"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇶🇦",
        "response": "قطر"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇦🇪",
        "response": "الإمارات"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇩🇿",
        "response": "الجزائر"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇲🇦",
        "response": "المغرب"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇪🇬",
        "response": "مصر"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇮🇩",
        "response": "إندونيسيا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇹🇷",
        "response": "تركيا"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇵🇰",
        "response": "باكستان"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇮🇷",
        "response": "إيران"
    },
        {
       "question": "🇸🇦",
        "response": "السعودية"
    },
    {
       "question": "🇸🇬",
       "response": "سنغافورة"
}
      ]